Alifia Syalsabila

Front-end Web Developer

A front-end developer with more than 1-year of experience. I enjoy coding exploration as I can adapt easily and learn new things quickly. During my previous career, I can collaborate well with my teammates so that the work can be completed successfully in due time.

Address

Tanimulya, Ngamprah, KBB

Contact

linkedin.com/in/alifiasy in

alifiasyalsabila96@gmail.com

+62 89988933081

github.com/alifiasyalsa &

Click here for my portfolio

Work Experience



Front-end Developer | PT. Sinergi Inti Dinamika

November 2021 - now (1 year, 4 months)

- Improve an efficient clinical information system by implementing atomic design using Core UI & React JS.
- Develop features like odontograms, medical records, gueues, etc using Laravel & React JS.
- Assist in system migration from Laravel to React JS.
- Fix bugs in the clinical information system using Laravel.
- Create technical documentation for clinical information systems using JS Docs



Intern | PT. Digital Oasis

August 2020 - December 2020 (4 months)

- Debugging and bugs fixing CELOE application search and sort feature using Codelgniter.
- Develop an information system for reporting the work progress of Digital Oasis internal employees with Codelgniter, Bootstrap, and MySQL.
- Create a user manual for the CELOE digital learning application.

ComLabs Intern | Comlabs USDI ITB

April 2016 - July 2016 (4 months)

- Develop cash & finance applications for internal Comlabs using Codelgniter.
- Redesign the inventory application for the Comlabs canteen with Codelgniter and Bootstrap

Skills

Programming Language

Proficient in PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, SQL, HTML, and CSS. Experienced in Java, Python, and C++.

Library & Frameworks

Proficient in React JS, Next JS, Core UI, Bootstrap, Code Igniter, Laravel, and JQuery. Experienced in Tailwind CSS.

Git, Postman, Netlify, WordPress, VSCode, Jira.

Project

llea article

Created an article catalog and an article reading page.

KMO Himaptika

Designed and built an online math competition application for IKIP Siliwangi.

GOR Panathayuda

Designed and built a GOR reservation admin application.

Education

Bachelor of Applied, Computer Engineering, and Informatics | **Polytechnic State of Bandung**

2017 - 2021

- Planned and organized KKN events attended by more than 100 participants.
- Doing research related to state management in Flutter